[{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":20309,"timeElapsed":82529},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980316168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":22293,"timeElapsed":104825},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5056,"timeElapsed":109882},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3820,"timeElapsed":113704},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3146,"timeElapsed":116852},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980339838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":11640,"timeElapsed":128495},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980351112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":11273,"timeElapsed":139769},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":11016,"timeElapsed":150787},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4330,"timeElapsed":155119},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9666,"timeElapsed":166914},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5438,"timeElapsed":172353},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3947,"timeElapsed":176301},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3616,"timeElapsed":179919},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3757,"timeElapsed":183677},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6951,"timeElapsed":190629},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3019,"timeElapsed":193649},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409604,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4610,"timeElapsed":198261},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4392,"timeElapsed":202654},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980418087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4088,"timeElapsed":206743},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":9843,"timeElapsed":218294},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2650,"timeElapsed":220945},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4775,"timeElapsed":225721},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4494,"timeElapsed":230216},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":7616,"timeElapsed":237833},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":12340,"timeElapsed":250175},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3614,"timeElapsed":253791},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4661,"timeElapsed":258453},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":13448,"timeElapsed":271902},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":14911,"timeElapsed":288763},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4190,"timeElapsed":292953},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3513,"timeElapsed":296468},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3972,"timeElapsed":300441},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2533,"timeElapsed":302976},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":11078,"timeElapsed":314055},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2036,"timeElapsed":316092},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6314,"timeElapsed":322409},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6749,"timeElapsed":329159},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":8900,"timeElapsed":339511},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980553516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2661,"timeElapsed":342173},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":345051},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6799,"timeElapsed":351852},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4302,"timeElapsed":356154},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3883,"timeElapsed":360039},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":362063},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":20004,"timeElapsed":382068},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1909,"timeElapsed":383978},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8020,"timeElapsed":393057},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2546,"timeElapsed":395604},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2507,"timeElapsed":398112},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2444,"timeElapsed":400558},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2354,"timeElapsed":402913},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":405905},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4010,"timeElapsed":409916},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3831,"timeElapsed":413749},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1591,"timeElapsed":415341},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":8683,"timeElapsed":425794},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2699,"timeElapsed":428494},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2444,"timeElapsed":430939},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4443,"timeElapsed":435383},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4252,"timeElapsed":439636},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":6900,"timeElapsed":446538},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1691,"timeElapsed":448230},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3641,"timeElapsed":451872},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667520,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4303,"timeElapsed":456177},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3194,"timeElapsed":459373},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7893,"timeElapsed":468591},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":470743},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":473875},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":477924},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":480254},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3143,"timeElapsed":483399},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":485207},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4927,"timeElapsed":490135},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2252,"timeElapsed":492388},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980713179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7982,"timeElapsed":501836},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2009,"timeElapsed":503846},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980717723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2532,"timeElapsed":506380},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2520,"timeElapsed":508902},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3448,"timeElapsed":512351},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2788,"timeElapsed":515140},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":517660},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4175,"timeElapsed":521837},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2672,"timeElapsed":524510},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7803,"timeElapsed":533828},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3361,"timeElapsed":537191},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7383,"timeElapsed":544575},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2865,"timeElapsed":547441},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3207,"timeElapsed":550649},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2723,"timeElapsed":553374},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2660,"timeElapsed":556036},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4531,"timeElapsed":560568},{"subjectID":"64oykh2oq4","prolificID":"637545d6428d85daeedc3df5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2640d369a872b7978ba","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2634,"timeElapsed":563203}]